Sweet Home with Shizuka-chan
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
I wonder what Shizuka-chan is doing...
Thank you, I needed a scarf like this!
I'm happy to lend it to you.
Doraemon, are you listening to me?
What happened to you so suddenly?
Didn't we confirmed that I'll marry Shizuka-chan using the Time Machine?
Yes, we did. But what's wrong now?
I can't let Dekisugi flirt with Shizuka-chan!
Dekisugi asked for her scarf...
So you're jealous of him!
Come, follow me.
Sweet Home!
What's this?
if you bring a girl you have crush on...
she'll start loving you after entering the home..
But keep in mind, that it only works as long as both of you are inside the home.
Let's give it a try!
This home is so spacious!
It even has a bathroom and kitchen.
Switch on!
So pretty!
Did you like it?
I'm in love with Nobita-kun!
Stop, you're so gross!
Nobita-kun!
DIsgusting!
After entering the house the second person to enter...
will fall in love with the first person to enter the home.
Gotcha!
i'll go invite Shizuka-chan!
Oh my, Nobita-san!
I'm currently doing my homework.
Let's do it slowly together, in our sweet home!
Sweet Home?
But with you...?
Oh, please...
What a nice home!
I've built it for us!
You mean it?
Yup.
Well, I'm coming in!
In this house, the order of entering the house is very important, you see.
Come in!
Congragulations, Nobita-kun!
How beautiful!
I wonder what happened to me?
My heart is so pounding.
It's working!
I love you, Nobita-san!
I did it~!
Nobita-san don't you feel the pounding of my heart?
Not really. Don't you love Dekisugi more than me, though?
You gave him your scarf after all.
Not true!
It's just a return of a favor.
He always helps me do my homework after all.
You are the only boy I love.
Sorry, I see.
So please cheer up!
This is the Kitchen.
How spacious!
Here's the bathroom!
Wonderful! I've always wanted to take bath in a bathroom like this.
Great!
You don't need my help anymore, so I'm going home!
I'm so happy!
Let's rest.  I love kitchen.
Me too.
When I see that shape, it reminds me of butt ...
I'll bake hotcake just for you, in the kitchen.
I'm so happy to hear that!
Just wait a minute...
I'll bring the ingredients.
Come back quickly!
Oh, my!
I don't have time for this!
Oh, Giko-chan?
Have you seen Nobita-kun?
I want to model the protagonist of my new gag Manga after him.
He's over there.
How nice it'd be to taste the hotcake baked by Shizuka-chan.
I wonder if she's home?
Oh, you sure took so long!
Nobita-san!
Oh no!
Giko, get back to your senses!
I wonder what was I doing here?
Huh, where is Nobita-kun?
oh, Giko!
Big bro, I have a problem!
What? You wanted to model character after him, but he ran away?
Alright, Big Bro will catch him for you!
Count me in!
Please ocme back!
No, I feel weird inside there.
Don't you want to take bath in that bathroom?
But I have to finish my homeowrk.
Oh, come on...
Will you join me?
I've to water the plants.
Come on, Shizuka-chan!
What's with that small home?
No one's in.
Suneo, you're so manly and handsome.
Giant, why did your face suddenly changed like this?
Suneo, I love you.
I'm so shy!
Suneo, do you love me?
Giant, come back to your senses!
But I can't! Please say "I love you" to me.
Wait, Suneo!
Are you ok, Giant?
Damn you, how dare you run from me!
I wonder what Nobita-kun is up to.
What are you doing here?